Guide to the Edwin and Terry Murray Collection of Newsprint Comic Strips RL.11749
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Clipped newsprint comic strips, 1920s-1980s; 1
  - Kerry Drake, Steve Roper, and Steve Canyon, 1959-1960 (Box 103)
  - Kerry Drake, Steve Roper, and Steve Canyon, 1960-1964 (Box 103)
  - King Aroo, 1951-1952 (Box 94)
  - King Aroo, 1952 (Box 40)
  - King Aroo, 1953 (Box 94)
  - King Aroo, 1953-1954 (Box 94)
  - King Aroo, 1954 (Box 40)
  - King Aroo, 1954 (Box 40)
  - King Aroo, 1954-1955 (Box 94)
  - King Aroo, 1955 Jan-May (Box 40)
  - Little Orphan Annie, 1929, 1940 (Box 92)
  - Mandrake, 1958 Aug-Nov (Box 81)
  - Mandrake the Magician, 1953 (Box 58)
  - Mandrake the Magician, 1954 (Box 58)
  - Mandrake the Magician, 1954 (Box 58)
  - Mandrake the Magician, 1954 (Box 79)
  - Mandrake the Magician, 1963 (Box 100)
  - Mandrake the Magician, 1967 (Box 100)
  - Mark Trail, Big Ben Bolt, Phantom, and Henry, 1954 (Box 94)
  - Mark Trail, Big Ben Bolt, Phantom, and Henry, 1955 (Box 94)
  - Mark Trail, Big Ben Bolt, Phantom, and Henry, 1955 (Box 95)
  - Mark Trail, Big Ben Bolt, Phantom, and Henry, 1956; 3 folders (Box 95)
  - Mark Trail, Big Ben Bolt, Phantom, and Henry, 1957 (Box 95)
  - Mark Trail, 1950s; 5 folders (Box 30)
  - Mark Trail, 1960s; 8 folders (Box 30)
  - Mary Worth, 1951-1953; scattered (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1954-1955; scattered (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1956; scattered (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1957 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1957 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1958 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1959 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1960 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1960 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1961 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1961 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1962 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1964 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1965 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1965 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1966 (Box 56)
  - Mary Worth, 1966, 1957 (Box 56)
  - Moon Mullins, 1924; Scattered (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1925; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1926; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1927; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1929-1933 (Box 92)
  - Moon Mullins, 1929, 1935 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1931; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1932 Jan-Jun (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1932 Jul-Dec (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1933 Jan-Jun (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1933 Jul-Dec (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1934 Jan-Jun (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1934 Jul-Dec (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1935 Jan-Jun (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1935 Jul-Dec (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1936; 2 folders (Box 24)
  - Moon Mullins, 1936 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1936 Jan-Jun, 1937 Jan (Box 25)
  - Moon Mullins, 1937 Jul-Dec (Box 25)
  - Moon Mullins, 1937 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1938; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Moon Mullins, 1938 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1939 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1940 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1941 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1941-1947 (Box 91)
  - Moon Mullins, 1942 Jan-Jun (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1942 Jul-Dec (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1942 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1943 (Box 96)
  - Moon Mullins, 1943-1945 (Box 25)
  - Moon Mullins, 1944 (Box 97)
  - Moon Mullins, 1945 (Box 97)
  - Moon Mullins, 1946 Feb-Jun (Box 25)
  - Moon Mullins, 1946 Jul-Dec (Box 25)
  - Moon Mullins, 1947 (Box 91)
  - Moon Mullins, 1948 (Box 97)
  - Moon Mullins, 1948 Jan-Jun (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1948 Jul-Nov (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1949 (Box 97)
  - Moon Mullins, 1950 (Box 97)
  - Moon Mullins, 1951-1953 (Box 97)
  - Moon Mullins, 1951 Jul-Dec (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1952 (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1952 (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1953 (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1953 (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1953-1954 (Box 97)
  - Moon Mullins, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1955 (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1956 Jan-Jun (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1956 Jul-Dec (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1957 Jan-Jun (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1957 Jul-Dec (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1958 Jan-Jun (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1958 Jul-Dec (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1959 Jan-Jun (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1959 Jul-Dec (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1960 Jan-Jun (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1960 Jul-Dec (Box 32)
  - Moon Mullins, 1964 (Box 25)
  - Moon Mullins, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 25)
  - Mr. Holiday, 1950 (Box 80)
  - Mrs. Fitz's Flat/ The Jackson Twins, 1959 (Box 80)
  - Mrs. Fitz's Flats, 1958; Scattered (Box 37)
  - Mrs. Fitz's Flats, 1961; Scattered (Box 51)
  - Mrs. Fitz's Flats, 1962; Scattered (Box 37)
  - On Stage, 1966; Scattered (Box 28)
  - On Stage, 1957-1958 (Box 26)
  - On Stage, 1957-1958 (Box 91)
  - On Stage, 1958-1959 (Box 91)
  - On Stage, 1959-1960 (Box 91)
  - On Stage: Mary Perkins, 1960-1962 (Box 91)
  - On Stage: Mary Perkins, 1962-1963 (Box 91)
  - On Stage: Mary Perkins, 1963-1965 (Box 97)
  - On Stage: Mary Perkins, 1965-1966 (Box 97)
  - On Stage, 1962 Jan-Jun (Box 28)
  - On Stage, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 28)
  - On Stage, 1963 Jan, Sep-Dec (Box 28)
  - On Stage, 1964 Jan-Jun (Box 28)
  - On Stage, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 28)
  - On Stage, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 28)
  - Out Our Way, 1930 (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1931 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1931 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1932 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1932 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1934 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1934 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1935 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1935 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1936 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1936 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1937 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1937 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1938 Jan-Apr (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1938 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1939 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1939 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1940 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1940 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1941 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1941 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1942 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1942 Jul-Dec (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1943 Jan-Jun (Box 22)
  - Out Our Way, 1943 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1945 Jan-Jun (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1945 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1948 Jan-Jun (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1948 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1956 (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1957 Jan-Jun (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1957 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1958 Jan-Jun (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1958 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1959 Jan-May 13 (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1961 Jan-Jun (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1961 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1962 Jan-Jul (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1962 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1963 Jan-Jun (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1963 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1964 Feb 29-Jun (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 55)
  - Out Our Way, 1966 Jan-Aug (Box 55)
  - Perry Mason, 1950-1952 (Box 26)
  - Phantom, 1960 (Box 100)
  - Phantom, 1960-1962 (Box 92)
  - Phantom, 1962-1963 (Box 92)
  - Phantom, 1963-1965 (Box 92)
  - Phantom, 1964 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Phantom, 1964 Mar 24-Jun (Box 54)
  - Phantom, 1965 (Box 92)
  - Phantom, 1965 Jan-Jun (Box 54)
  - Phantom, 1965 Jul-Dec (Box 54)
  - Phantom, 1966 Jan-Aug 1 (Box 54)
  - Phantom, 1966 (Box 92)
  - Popeye, 1944 Jan-Jun (Box 36)
  - Popeye, 1944 Jul-Dec (Box 36)
  - Popeye, 1945; Scattered (Box 36)
  - Popeye, 1946 Aug-Dec (Box 36)
  - Popeye, 1946 Feb-Jul (Box 36)
  - Popeye, 1947 Jan-May 23 (Box 36)
  - Popeye, 1947-1948; Scattered (Box 37)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1966 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1967 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1967 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1968 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1968 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1969 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1969 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1970 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1970 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1972 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1972 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1973 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1973 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1974 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1974 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1975 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1975 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1976 Jan-Jun (Box 44)
  - Priscilla's Pop, 1976 Jul-Dec (Box 44)
  - Red Ryder, 1940 Feb-Jun (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1940 Jul-Nov (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1941 Aug-Nov (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1941 Feb-May (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1943 Jan-Jun (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1943 Jul-Dec (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1944 Jan-Jun (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1944 Jul-Dec (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1945 Jan-Jun (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1945 Jul-Dec (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1946 Jan-Jun (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1946 Jul-Dec (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1947 Jan-Jun (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1947 Jul-Dec (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1948 Jan-May (Box 31)
  - Red Ryder, 1948 Jun-Oct (Box 31)
  - Rick O'Shay, 1960-1966 (Box 93)
  - Rick O'Shay, 1966; Scattered (Box 28)
  - Rick O'Shay, 1966-1968 (Box 93)
  - RIP Kirby, 1951 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1952 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1952 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1953 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1953 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1954 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1954 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1955 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1955 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1956 (Box 76)
  - RIP Kirby, 1957 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1957 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1958 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1959 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1959 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1960 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1960 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1961 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1961 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1962 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1962 (Box 77)
  - RIP Kirby, 1963 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1963 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1964 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1964 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1965 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1965 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1965 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1966 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1967 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1968 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1968 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1969 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1970 (Box 78)
  - RIP Kirby, 1970 (Box 79)
  - RIP Kirby, 1971 (Box 79)
  - Robin Malone, 1967 (Box 26)
  - Roy Rogers, 1954-1955 (Box 100)
  - The Saint, 1948 Sep-Dec (Box 49)
  - The Saint, 1949 (Box 99)
  - Sky Masters, 1959 (Box 57)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1937 (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1938; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1939; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1941; 2 folders (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1942 Jan-Aug (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1944 (Box 99)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1944 Jan-Jun (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1944 Jul-Nov (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1945-1948 (Box 97)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1945 Jan-Jun (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1945 Jul-Dec (Box 25)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1946 Jan-Jun (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1946 Jul-Dec (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1947-1953 (Box 97)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1947 Feb-Jul (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1947 Jul-Dec (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1948 Jan-Jun (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1948 Jul-Dec (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1949-1956 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1949 Jan-Jun (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1949 Jul-Dec (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1950 Jan-Jun (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1950 Jul-Dec (Box 26)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1951 Jul-Dec (Box 43)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1952 (Box 43)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1956-1958 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1958-1959 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1959-1960 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1960-1961 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1961-1963 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1963-1964 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1964-1965 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1965-1967 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1967-1968 (Box 93)
  - Smilin' Jack, 1968-1969 (Box 93)
  - Steve Canyon, 1971-1972 (Box 81)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1947 (Box 67)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1947-1950; unsorted (Box 67)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1948 (Box 67)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1949 (Box 67)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1950 (Box 68)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1951 (Box 68)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1952 (Box 68)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1953 (Box 68)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1954 (Box 69)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1955 (Box 69)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1956 (Box 69)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1957 (Box 69)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1958 (Box 70)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1959 (Box 70)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1960 (Box 70)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1961 (Box 70)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1962 (Box 71)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1963 (Box 71)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1964 (Box 71)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1965 (Box 71)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1966 (Box 72)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1967 (Box 72)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1968 (Box 72)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1969 (Box 72)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1970 (Box 73)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1971 (Box 73)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1972 (Box 73)
  - Steve Canyon Loose Strips, 1973 (Box 73)
  - Steve Roper, 1949 Jan-Jun (Box 36)
  - Steve Roper, 1949 Jul-Dec (Box 36)
  - Steve Roper, 1949; 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Steve Roper, 1956; 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Steve Roper, 1956; 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Steve Roper, 1964 (Box 80)
  - Steve Roper, 1964-1965 (Box 100)
  - Steve Roper, 1965 (Box 100)
  - Steve Roper, 1965; 2 folders (Box 80)
  - Steve Roper, 1966 (Box 80)
  - Superman, 1959 (Box 42)
  - Superman, 1959 (Box 42)
  - Superman, 1960 (Box 42)
  - Superman, 1960 (Box 42)
  - Superman, 1961 (Box 42)
  - Superman, 1962 (Box 42)
  - Superman, 1962 (Box 42)
  - Superman, 1963 (Box 42)
  - Tales of the Green Berets, 1965 (Box 26)
  - Tales of the Green Beret, 1966 (Box 93)
  - Tales of the Green Beret, 1966 Apr-Aug (Box 42)
  - The Green Beret, 1966-1967 (Box 23)
  - The Green Beret, 1967-1968 (Box 23)
  - Tarzan, 1947-1949 (Box 20)
  - Terry and the Pirates, 1947 Jan-Jun (Box 26)
  - Terry and the Pirates, 1947 Jul-Dec (Box 26)
  - Thorn McBride, 1960 (Box 80)
  - Twin Earths, 1952 (Box 81)
  - Twin Earths, 1952 (Box 81)
  - Twin Earths, 1953 Jan-Jun (Box 81)
  - Twin Earths, 1953 Jul-Dec (Box 81)
  - Twin Earths, 1954 Jan-Jun (Box 81)
  - Twin Earths, 1954 Jul-Dec (Box 81)
  - Twin Earths, 1955 (Box 81)
  - Twin Earths, 1955 (Box 81)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1943 (Box 26)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1943 (Box 81)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1943 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1944 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1944 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1945 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1945 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1946 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1946 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1947 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1947 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1948 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1949 (Box 82)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1950 Jan-Jun (Box 45)
  - Wash Tubbs, 1950 Jul-Dec (Box 45)
  - The Wizard of Id, 1960 (Box 26)
  - The Wizard of Id, 1966 (Box 26)
  - The Wizard of Id, 1969 Aug-Dec (Box 26)
  - The Wizard of Id, 1969 Feb-Jun (Box 26)
  - The Wizard of Id, 1970 Jan-Jun (Box 26)
  - The Wizard of Id, 1970 Jul-Dec (Box 26)
- Newspaper comic sections (Funnies), 1925-1988; 2
  Series contains newspaper comic sections for assorted newspapers, collected by the Murrays documenting the range of comic strip titles published within each newspaper. Runs are incomplete and scattered, and the physical condition of each newspaper issue varies.
  - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1968-1981
    Comic strips include: Agatha Crumm, Andy Capp, Archie, BC, Beetle Bailey, Blondie, Boner's Ark, Carrier-toons, Condorman, Doonsebury, Emmy Lou, Funland, Hagär, Henry, Hi & Lois, Hubert, Inside Woody Allen, Life's Like That, Lil Abner, Little Iodine, The Lockhorns, Louie, Mark Trail, Miss Peach, Mr. Abernathy, Mutt & Jeff, Nancy, The North-Avenue-Irregulars, Our New Age, Peanuts, Pooley's World, Prince Valiant, Scamp, Ripley's Believe it or Not, Snuffy Smith, Star Wars, Steve Canyon, Tarzan, the black hole, They'll Do It Everytime, Uncle Remus, and Wizard of ID.
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1968 Jan (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1968 Feb-Mar (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1968 Apr-May (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1968 Jun-Jul (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1968 Aug-Sep (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1968 Oct-Nov (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1968 Dec-1969 Jan (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1969 Feb-Mar (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1969 Apr-May (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1969 Jun-July (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1969 Aug-Sep (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1969 Oct-Nov (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1969 Dec-1970 Jan (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1970 Feb-Mar (Box 84)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1970 Apr-May (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1970 Jun-Jul (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1970 Aug-Sep (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1970 Oct-Nov (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1970 Dec-1971 Jan (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1971 Feb-Mar (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1971 Apr-May (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1971 Jun-Jul (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1971 Aug-Sep (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1971 Oct-Nov (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1971 Dec-1972 Jan (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1972 Feb-Mar (Box 85)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1972 Apr-May (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1972 Jun-Jul (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1972 Aug-Sep (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1972 Oct-Nov (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1972 Dec-1973 Jan (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1973 Feb-Mar (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1973 Apr-May (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1973 Jun-Jul (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1973 Aug-Sep (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1973 Oct-Nov (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1973 Dec-1974 Jan (Box 86)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1974 Feb-Mar (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1974 Apr-May (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1974 Jun-Jul (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1974 Aug-Sep (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1974 Oct-Nov (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1974 Dec-1975 Jan (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1975 Feb-Mar (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1975 Apr-May (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1975 Jun-Jul (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1975 Aug-Sep (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1975 Oct-Nov (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1975 Dec-1976 Jan (Box 87)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1976 Feb-Mar (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1976 Apr-May (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1976 Jun-Jul (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1976 Aug-Sep (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1976 Oct-Nov (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1976 Dec-1977 Jan (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1977 Feb-Mar (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1977 Apr-May (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1977 Jun-Jul (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1977 Aug-Sep (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1977 Oct-Nov (Box 88)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1977 Nov-1978 Jan (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1978 Feb-Mar (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1978 Apr-May (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1978 Jun-Jul (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1978 Aug-Sep (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1978 Oct-Nov (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1978 Dec-1979 Jan (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1979 Feb-Mar (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1979 Apr-May (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1979 Jun-Jul (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1979 Aug-Sep (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1979 Oct-Nov (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1979 Dec-1980 Jan (Box 89)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1980 Feb-Mar (Box 90)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1980 Apr-May (Box 90)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1980 Jun-Jul (Box 90)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1980 Aug-Sep (Box 90)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1980 Oct-Nov (Box 90)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1980 Dec-1981 Jan (Box 90)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1981 Feb-Mar (Box 90)
    - Asbury Park Sunday Press, 1981 Apr-May (Box 90)
  - The Chicago Defender, 1970-1972
    Includes Donald Duck, Etta Kett, Brick Bradford, Popeye, Big Ben Bolt, Secret Agent X9, Mickey Mouse, Flop Family, Henry, and othe cartoons scattered throughout.
    - The Chicago Defender, 1970 (Box 104)
    - The Chicago Defender, 1971 (Box 104)
    - The Chicago Defender, 1972 (Box 104)
  - Detroit Free Press, 1925-1927
    Comics included: The Gumps, The Captain and the Kids, Winnie Winkle, Gasoline Alley, Mr. and Mrs., Cicero Sapp, Moon Mullins, Peter Rabbit, Nize Baby.
    Sections are damaged and run is incomplete.
    - Detroit Free Press comics sections, 1925-1927 (Box 20)
  - The Citizen and the Times (Asheville, N.C.) special 69th anniversary issue with commemorative comics section, 1939 Jan. 28 (Box 20)
  - The Durham Sun, 1921-1932, 1953
    Includes Out Our Way, Salesman Sam, Side Glances, S'matter Pop, The Newf Angles, Wash Tubbs
    - The Durham Sun, 1921 Apr, 1928-1929 Apr-Mar (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1929 Mar - Apr (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1929 May-Jun (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1929 Jul-Aug (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1929 Jul-Sep (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1929 Sep-Dec (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1929-1930 Dec-Jan (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1930 Jan-Mar (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1930 Mar (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1930 Apr-Jul (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1930 Jul-Sep (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1931-1932 Sep-Dec (Box 102)
    - The Durham Sun, 1953 March 4 (Box 101)
      Includes Dick Tracy, Li'l Abner, Chris Welkin Planeteer, Rex Morgan M.D, Captain Easy, Steve Canyon, Toots and Casper, Moon Mullins, Jungle Jim, The Willets Out Our Way, Mutt and Jeff, and Life's Like That
  - Dallas Morning News, 1941
    Comic strips include: Captain Easy, Out Our Way, The Spirit, Ella Cinders, Abbie an' Slats, Pretty Peggy, Chief Wahoo, Dumb Dora, Private Lives, Double Trouble Bureau, Dan Dunn, Mary Worth's Family.
    Scattered issues.
    - Dallas Morning News, 1941 (Box 20)
  - Durham Morning Herald, 1953
    Includes Blondie, Buz Sawyer, Gasoline Alley, The Gumps, Henry, Joe Palooka, Kerry Drake, Mary Worth, Nancy, Smilin' Jack, Snookums, The Katzenjammer Kids, The Phantom, and The Sad Sack
    - Durham Morning Herald, 1953 May-Jun (Box 96)
    - Durham Morning Herald, 1953 Jun-Jul (Box 96)
    - Durham Morning Herald, 1953 Jul-Aug (Box 96)
  - The Greenville News, 1952-1968
    Includes Big Ben Bolt, Blondie, Boots, Bringing Up Father, Buck Rogers, Buz Sawyer, Captain Easy, Carnival, Colonel Potter, Dick Tracy, Dixie Dugan, Gasoline Alley, Harold Teen, Herby, Jungle Jim, The Karzenjammer Kids, Kitty Higgens, Li'l Abner, Little Debbie, Little Iodine, Little Joe, Little Orphan, Annie, Mary Worth, Mickey Finn, Mickey Mouse, Moon Mullins, Mutt and Jeff, Out Our Way, Penny, The Phantom, Pogo, Right Around Home with Myrtle, The Saint, Smilin' Jack, Snookums, Steve Canyon, Terry and the Pirates, They'll Do It Every Time, Uncle Remus, Winnie Winkle
    - The Greenville News, 1952 (Box 101)
    - The Greenville News, 1953-1957 (Box 101)
    - The Greenville News, 1958-1968 (Box 101)
  - Greenville Piedmont, 1952 March 1, 1953 January 17 (Box 101)
    2 issues. Includes Alley Oop, Boots, Bugs Bunny, Captain Easy, Donald Duck, Joe Palooka, Moon Mullins, Mr. and Mrs., Nancy, Our Boarding House, Out Our Way, Priscilla, Red Ryder, and Vic Flint
  - The Milwakee Journal Comics Section, 1936; scattered (Box 60)
  - New Orleans Times Picayune, 1949-1950